{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685698589","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685698589"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685703517","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685703517"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685707129","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685707129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685712596","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685712596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685716234","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685716234"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685719882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685719882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685724630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685724630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685728474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685728474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685732046","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685732046"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685735719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685735719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685739891","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685739891"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685743552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685743552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685747627","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685747626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685752904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685752904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685754807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685754807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685812746","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685812746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685825214","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685825214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" e309b4aa-02e1-4850-a83d-a9cb424f7b7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685834719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685834719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" d565208a-5bfc-487d-8430-bfbfc86559c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685838469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685838468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" d565208a-5bfc-487d-8430-bfbfc86559c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685842029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685842029"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203448"," gameId":" d565208a-5bfc-487d-8430-bfbfc86559c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}